export const Quizdata = [
    {
        Question: "Sun is a _______",
        Options: ["planet", "star", "galaxy", "Universe"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        Question: "Which is a biggest planet in our solarsystem ?",
        Options: ["earth", "venus", "jupiter", "saturn"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question: "Which planet has biggest rings ?",
        Options: ["mars", "saturn", "neptune", "Mercury"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        Question: "Which planet is nearest to the sun ?",
        Options: ["venus", "earth", "mars", "Mercury"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        Question: "Which planet is so cold?",
        Options: ["neptune", "saturn", "uranus", "jupiter"],
        answer: 2
    }
]

export const exoplanetsQuizdata = [
    {
        Question: "In 1992, astronomers Aleksander Wolszczan and Dale Frail found the first exoplanets around what unusual object?",
        Options: ["A pulsar", "A marsbar", "A quasar", "A gamma ray burster"],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        Question: "51 Pegasi b is the first exoplanet discovered around a sun-like star. It has an orbital period of only 4 earth days and is thus known as the prototype of what kind of planet?",
        Options: ["Near Neptunian", "Ice giant", "Hot Jupiter", "Brown dwarf"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the name of the proposed European Space Agency probe to detect earth-like planets?",
        Options: ["Erasmus", "Bigeye", "Newton", "Darwin"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        Question: "The 'circumstellar habitable zone' is the area around a star where liquid water, and therefore life might exist. By what curious name is it more commonly known?",
        Options: ["Gaia zone", "Chthonian region", "Hydrous hemisphere", "Goldilocks zone"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        Question: "Which of these techniques has NOT been used to detect exoplanets?",
        Options: ["Radial velocity", "Transit method", "Gravitational microlensing", "Ferengian diffraction"],
        answer: 3
    }
]